A Guide to the Winthrop Rockefeller Foundation records FA248
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Grants, 1972-2001; 2 (Reel 15, Frame 203)
  - Programs, 1976-2001; 1 (Reel 15, Frame 204)
    - Arkansas Family Day Care Providers for Quality Child Care, Incorporated, 79-1006, 1979 (Reel 27, Frame 262)
    - Arkansas Family Planning Council, Teenage Pregnancy, 82-263, 1982 (Reel 27, Frame 284)
    - Arkansas Family Planning Council, 83-322, 1983 (Reel 27, Frame 300)
    - Arkansas Family Planning Council, 83-339, 1983-1984 (Reel 27, Frame 337)
    - Arkansas Family Planning Council, 84-396, 1984-1985 (Reel 27, Frame 363)
    - Arkansas Family Planning Council, 85-477, 1985-1986 (Reel 27, Frame 392)
    - Arkansas Federated Children, Incorporated, 85-494, 1985-1987 (Reel 27, Frame 409)
    - Arkansas Foundation of Associated Colleges, 82-264, 1982 (Reel 27, Frame 432)
    - Arkansas for Drug Free Youth, Union City, 95-169, 1995-1999 (Reel 27, Frame 442)
    - Arkansas Gay and Lesbian Task Force, 95-174, 1995-1997 (Reel 27, Frame 561)
    - Arkansas Grantseekers Horizon, Professional Services Agreement, 1988-1990 (Reel 27, Frame 691)
    - Arkansas Historical Association, 84-385, 1984-1986 (Reel 27, Frame 793)
    - Arkansas Human Development Corporation, 85-512, 1985-1986 (Reel 27, Frame 818)
    - Arkansas Human Development Corporation, 87-827, 1987-1988 (Reel 27, Frame 863)
    - Arkansas Human Development Corporation, 88-140, 1988-1990 (Reel 27, Frame 886)
    - Arkansas Human Development Corporation, 91-72, Original Proposal-Year One, 1991-1993 (Reel 27, Frame 905)
    - Arkansas Human Development Corporation, 91-72, Year Two-Year Three, 1992-1994 (Reel 27, Frame 1071)
    - Arkansas Humanities Council, Original Proposal-Grant Agreement, 1991-1994 (Reel 28, Frame 1)
      Grant number: 92-185 & 94-97
    - Arkansas Humanities Council, 92-185 & 94-97, 92-185 Year One-Year Three and 94-97 Year Two, 1993-1995 (Reel 28, Frame 170)
    - Arkansas Humanities Council, 96-43, 1996-2001 (Reel 28, Frame 376)
    - Arkansas Institute for Social Justice, Incorporated, 86-606, 1986-1987 (Reel 28, Frame 679)
    - Arkansas Institute for Social Justice, Incorporated, 87-744/87-791/87-856, 1987-1988 (Reel 28, Frame 706)
    - Arkansas Institute for Social Justice, Incorporated, 88-42, 1988-1991 (Reel 28, Frame 730)
    - Arkansas Institute for Social Justice, Incorporated, 88-136, 1988-1989 (Reel 28, Frame 795)
    - Arkansas Institute for Social Justice, Incorporated, Reverned Delton Jones, Professional Services Agreement, 1993 (Reel 28, Frame 812)
    - Arkansas Inter-faith Conference, Formerly Arkansas Partners in Education, Original Proposal-Grant Agreement, 1994-1996 (Reel 28, Frame 815)
      Grant number: 94-163
    - Arkansas Inter-faith Conference, Formerly Arkansas Partners in Education, 94-163, Year One, 1995-1996 (Reel 28, Frame 947)
    - Arkansas Inter-faith Conference, Formerly Arkansas Partners in Education, 94-163, Year Two, 1995-1997 (Reel 29, Frame 1)
    - Arkansas Inter-Faith Hunger Task Force, Rice Depot, 82-285, 1982 (Reel 29, Frame 221)
    - Arkansas Inter-Faith Hunger Task Force, 82-309, 1983-1984 (Reel 29, Frame 232)
    - Arkansas Inter-Faith Hunger Task Force, 83-377, 1983-1984 (Reel 29, Frame 248)
    - Arkansas Inter-Faith Hunger Task Force, 84-415, 1984-1985 (Reel 29, Frame 278)
    - Arkansas Inter-Faith Hunger Task Force, 84-453, 1984-1985 (Reel 29, Frame 307)
    - Arkansas Inter-Faith Hunger Task Force, 85-509, 1985-1986 (Reel 29, Frame 347)
    - Arkansas Land and Farm Development Corporation, 81-1000, 1981 (Reel 29, Frame 379)
    - Arkansas Land and Farm Development Corporation, 82-287, 1982 (Reel 29, Frame 397)
    - Arkansas Land and Farm Development Corporation, 83-347, 1983-1984 (Reel 29, Frame 423)
    - Arkansas Land and Farm Development Corporation, 85-484, 1985-1986 (Reel 29, Frame 454)
    - Arkansas Land and Farm Development Corporation, 86-707, 1986-1988 (Reel 29, Frame 504)
    - Arkansas Land and Farm Development Corporation, 87-849, 1987-1988 (Reel 29, Frame 528)
    - Arkansas Land and Farm Development Corporation, 88-167, 1988-1989 (Reel 29, Frame 550)
    - Arkansas Land and Farm Development Corporation, Original Proposal-Grant Agreement, 1990-1993 (Reel 29, Frame 571)
      Grant number: 90-131
    - Arkansas Land and Farm Development Corporation, 90-131, Year One-Year Three, 1989-1993 (Reel 29, Frame 681)
    - Arkansas Land and Farm Development Corporation, Original Proposal-Grant Agreement, 1992-1998 (Reel 29, Frame 977)
      Grant number: 92-88
    - Arkansas Land and Farm Development Corporation, 92-88, Year One-Year Two, 1992-1994 (Reel 30, Frame 1)
    - Arkansas Land and Farm Development Corporation, 92-88, Year Three-Year Four, 1994-1996 (Reel 30, Frame 183)
    - Arkansas Land and Farm Development Corporation, 92-88, Year Five, 1996-1997 (Reel 30, Frame 514)
    - Arkansas Land and Farm Development Corporation, 93-222, 1993-1996 (Reel 30, Frame 678)
    - Arkansas Land and Farm Development Corporation, Planning Grant, 1994 (Reel 30, Frame 773)
    - Arkansas League of Nursing, Incorporated, Peace Links, International, 82-282, 1982 (Reel 30, Frame 788)
    - Arkansas Low Income Housing Coalition, 94-192, Original Proposal-Year One, 1994-1996 (Reel 30, Frame 797)
    - Arkansas Low Income Housing Coalition, 94-192, Year Two-Year Three, 1996-1999 (Reel 31, Frame 1)
    - Arkansas Museum of Science and History, 96-91, 1996-1999 (Reel 31, Frame 504)
    - The Arkansas Nature Conservancy, 83-344, 1983-1984 (Reel 31, Frame 612)
    - The Arkansas Nature Conservancy, 84-437, 1984-1985 (Reel 31, Frame 645)
    - The Arkansas Nature Conservancy, 85-531, 1985-1986 (Reel 31, Frame 690)
    - Arkansas Opera Theatre, 79-1007, 1979 (Reel 31, Frame 734)
    - Arkansas Partners in Education, Incorporated, 93-96, 1993-1995 (Reel 31, Frame 746)
    - Arkansas Performance Review Committee, 87-816, 1987-1988 (Reel 31, Frame 933)
    - Arkansas Public Policy Panel, Incorporated, 91-115, 1991-1994 (Reel 31, Frame 951)
    - Arkansas Public Policy Panel, Incorporated, 94-200, Original Proposal-Year One, 1994-1996 (Reel 32, Frame 1)
    - Arkansas Public Policy Panel, Incorporated, 94-200, Year Two-Year Three, 1995-1998 (Reel 32, Frame 176)
    - Arkansas Regional Minority Purchase Council, Incorporated, 92-111, 1992-1993 (Reel 32, Frame 382)
    - Arkansas Repertory Theatre, 78-1004, 1978 (Reel 32, Frame 456)
    - Arkansas Repertory Theatre, 93-255, Original Proposal-Year Two, 1993-1995 (Reel 32, Frame 467)
    - Arkansas Repertory Theatre, 93-255, Year Three, 1993-1997 (Reel 32, Frame 666)
    - Arkansas River Education Service Cooperative, 92-39, 1992-1994 (Reel 32, Frame 914)
    - Arkansas River Education Service Cooperative, 93-76, 1993-1995 (Reel 32, Frame 1013)
    - Arkansas River Education Service Cooperative, 95-99, 1995-1997 (Reel 33, Frame 1)
    - Arkansas River Valley Resources Conservation and Development Area, Incorporated, 95-84, 1995-1998 (Reel 33, Frame 97)
    - Arkansas Rural Development Commission, 95-81, 1995-2000 (Reel 33, Frame 216)
    - Arkansas School Boards Association, Tommy R. Venters, Professional Services Agreement, 1992 (Reel 33, Frame 466)
    - Arkansas School for Mathematics and Sciences, 94-119, 1994-1995 (Reel 33, Frame 472)
    - Arkansas School for the Blind, Principal School Improvements, 93-212, 1993-1997 (Reel 33, Frame 511)
    - Arkansas School for the Deaf, 88-97, 1988-1989 (Reel 33, Frame 676)
    - Arkansas School for the Deaf, 91-65, 1991 (Reel 33, Frame 693)
    - Arkansas School for the Deaf, 96-21, 1996 (Reel 33, Frame 746)
    - Arkansas Seniors Organized for Progress, Incorporated, 88-175, 1988-1990 (Reel 33, Frame 783)
    - Arkansas Seniors Organized for Progress, Incorporated, 91-150, 1992 (Reel 33, Frame 8110)
    - Arkansas Seniors Organized for Progress, Incorporated, 93-238, 1993-1994 (Reel 33, Frame 837)
    - Arkansas Seniors Organized for Progress, Incorporated, 95-143, 1994-1998 (Reel 33, Frame 884)
    - Arkansas Single Parent Scholarship Fund, 95-173, 1995-1999 (Reel 34, Frame 1)
    - Arkansas Single Parent Scholarship Fund, 96-90, 1996-1998 (Reel 34, Frame 384)
    - Arkansas Soil and Water Conservation, 88-26, 1988-1989 (Reel 34, Frame 500)
    - Arkansas State Council on Economic Education, 81-245, 1981 (Reel 34, Frame 529)
    - Arkansas State Education Department, 85-483, 1985-1986 (Reel 34, Frame 548)
    - Arkansas State Education Department, 86-694, 1986-1987 (Reel 34, Frame 586)
    - Arkansas State University, Mid-South Writing Project, 78-1005, 1978 (Reel 34, Frame 606)
    - Arkansas State University, Mid-South Writing Project, 79-1008, 1979 (Reel 34, Frame 617)
    - Arkansas State University, 92-83, 1992-1993 (Reel 34, Frame 627)
    - Arkansas State University, Break the Mold, 92-174, 1992-1995 (Reel 34, Frame 651)
    - Arkansas State University, Break the Mold, 92-175, 1992 (Reel 34, Frame 679)
    - Arkansas State University, 93-47, 1993-1997 (Reel 34, Frame 699)
    - Arkansas State University, Break the Mold, 93-249, 1992-1995 (Reel 34, Frame 910)
    - Arkansas State University, Break the Mold, 94-204, 1994-1999 (Reel 35, Frame 1)
    - Arkansas Tech University, 86-580, 1986 (Reel 35, Frame 337)
    - Arkansas Tech University, Break the Mold, 93-250, 1992-1997 (Reel 35, Frame 453)
    - Arkansas Tech University, Break the Mold, 94-205, 1994-1999 (Reel 35, Frame 692)
    - Arkansas Territorial Restoration Foundation, 92-84, 1992-1996 (Reel 35, Frame 863)
    - Arkansas Vocational Education Foundation, Incorporated, 87-755, 1987-1988 (Reel 35, Frame 886)
    - Arkansas Wildlife Federation, Incorporated, 87-785, 1987-1988 (Reel 35, Frame 905)
    - Arkansas Wildlife Federation, Incorporated, 93-239, 1993-1994 (Reel 35, Frame 1011)
    - Armorel School District, 95-11, 1995 (Reel 35, Frame 1043)
    - Artisan Source, Incorporated, 90-63, 1989-1991 (Reel 35)
    - Artisan Source, Incorporated, 91-149, 1991-1995 (Reel 36, Frame 1)
    - Arts Alive!, Incorporated, 91-142, 1991-1993 (Reel 36, Frame 254)
    - Arts Alive!, Incorporated, 93-142, Original Proposal, 1993-1995 (Reel 36, Frame 364)
    - Arts Alive!, Incorporated, Grant Agreement-Year Three, 1993-1996 (Reel 36, Frame 622)
      Grant number: 93-142
    - ARVAC, Incorporated, Rural Industries, Craft Division, 78-1001, 1978 (Reel 36, Frame 850)
    - ARVAC, Incorporated, CAA/ARVAC Rural Industries, Folk Craft Division, 79-1001, 1979 (Reel 36, Frame 864)
    - ARVAC, Incorporated, AVRAC Industries, Folk Craft Division, 86-643, 1986 (Reel 36, Frame 877)
    - ARVAC, Incorporated, 93-223, 1993-1998 (Reel 36, Frame 902)
    - Ashdown Public Schools, 87-695, 1988-1989 (Reel 37, Frame 1)
    - Associated Universities for Toxicological Research and Education, Formerly NCTR, Original Proposal-Grant Agreement, 1991-1993 (Reel 37, Frame 20)
      Grant number: 91-73
    - Associated Universities for Toxicological Research and Education, Formerly NCTR, 91-73, Year One-Year Three, 1991-1994 (Reel 37, Frame 230)
    - Association for Supervision and Curriculum Development, 92-187, Original Proposal-Year One, 1992-1996 (Reel 37, Frame 495)
    - Association for Supervision and Curriculum Development, 92-187, Year Two-Year Three, 1994-1997 (Reel 37, Frame 686)
    - Association for Supervision and Curriculum Development, 95-85, 1995-1998 (Reel 37, Frame 816)
    - Association of Black Engineers, 93-220, 1993-1998 (Reel 37, Frame 954)
    - Atkins School District, 90-79, 1990-1991 (Reel 38, Frame 1)
    - Atkins School District, Atkins Elementary School, 91-53, 1991-1992 (Reel 38, Frame 67)
    - Atkins School District, 95-56, 1995-1996 (Reel 38, Frame 112)
    - Augusta School District, 85-502, 1985-1986 (Reel 38, Frame 158)
    - Augusta School District, 86-712, 1986-1987 (Reel 38, Frame 189)
    - Augusta School District, Augusta Junior High School, 90-14, 1990-1991 (Reel 38, Frame 213)
    - Augusta School District, 92-60, 1992-1994 (Reel 38, Frame 255)
    - Augusta School District, 94-58, 1994-1995 (Reel 38, Frame 282)
    - Augusta School District, 95-16, 1995-1996 (Reel 38, Frame 315)
    - Baird Kurtz and Dobson, Professional Services Agreement, 1989 (Reel 38, Frame 350)
    - Bald Knob School District, 92-11, 1991-1992 (Reel 38, Frame 355)
    - Bald Knob School District, 94-17, 1994-1995 (Reel 38, Frame 388)
    - Banks, Sherman, Professional Services Agreement, 1985 (Reel 38, Frame 430)
    - Bankson, Warren, Professional Services Agreement, 1989 (Reel 38, Frame 443)
    - Barnsley, Janice, Professional Services Agreement, 1990 (Reel 38, Frame 448)
    - Batesville School District, West Elementary School, 89-13, 1989 (Reel 38, Frame 460)
    - Batesville School District, Batesville Junior High School, 89-14, 1989 (Reel 38, Frame 483)
    - Batesville School District, 94-144, 1994-1995 (Reel 38, Frame 497)
    - Batesville School District, 95-124, 1995-1996 (Reel 38, Frame 543)
    - Baxter County Library, 96-123, 1996-1998 (Reel 38, Frame 579)
    - Bay Public Schools, 85-535, 1985-1986 (Reel 38, Frame 628)
    - Bay Public Schools, 86-693, 1986-1988 (Reel 38, Frame 663)
    - Bay Public Schools, 87-819, 1987-1989 (Reel 38, Frame 683)
    - Ann Becker and Associates, Incorporated, Professional Services Agreement, 1986-1989 (Reel 38, Frame 705)
    - Beebe Public Schools, 88-67, 1988-1989 (Reel 38, Frame 736)
    - Bob Bell and Associates, Professional Services Agreement, 1990 (Reel 38, Frame 757)
    - Bennett, Michael, Professional Services Agreement, 1990 (Reel 38, Frame 765)
    - Benton Public Schools, 85-505, 1985-1986 (Reel 38, Frame 769)
    - Benton Public Schools, 86-617, 1986-1987 (Reel 38, Frame 797)
    - Benton Public Schools, Talents Unlimited, 87-741, 1987-1988 (Reel 38, Frame 822)
    - Benton Public Schools, Benton Middle School, 87-807, 1987-1988 (Reel 38, Frame 839)
    - Benton Public Schools, H. Perrin Elementary School, 91-12, 1991-1992 (Reel 38, Frame 858)
    - Benton Public Schools, 95-109, 1995-1996 (Reel 38, Frame 895)
    - Bentonville School District, Old High Elementary School, 89-37, 1989 (Reel 38, Frame 947)
    - Bentonville School District, Thomas Jefferson Elementary School, 92-165, 1992-1993 (Reel 38, Frame 962)
    - Bentonville School District, School Improvements, Original Proposal-Grant Agreement, 1993-1996 (Reel 38, Frame 1010)
      Grant number: 93-217
    - Bentonville School District, School Improvements, 93-217, Year One-Year Four, 1993-1999 (Reel 39, Frame 1)
    - Berryville Public Schools, 87-839, 1988-1989 (Reel 39, Frame 155)
    - Berryville Public Schools, 91-34, 1990-1991 (Reel 39, Frame 173)
    - Berryville Public Schools, 91-100, 1991-1992 (Reel 39, Frame 225)
    - Berryville Public Schools, 93-60, 1993-1994 (Reel 39, Frame 156)
    - Berryville Public Schools, 93-109, 1993-1994 (Reel 39, Frame 307)
    - Berryville Public Schools, 95-9, 1995-1996 (Reel 39, Frame 348)
    - Biggers-Reyno School District, 93-3, 1993 (Reel 39, Frame 396)
    - Bismarck Public Schools, Bismarck Elementary School, 89-77, 1989-1990 (Reel 39, Frame 432)
    - Bismarck Public Schools, 92-19, 1991-1993 (Reel 39, Frame 450)
    - Bismarck Public Schools, 93-19, 1993-1994 (Reel 39, Frame 487)
    - Black Community Developers Program, Incorporated, 89-71, 1989-1991 (Reel 39, Frame 531)
    - Blevins Public Schools, 89-105, 1989-1990 (Reel 39, Frame 551)
    - Blytheville Public Schools, 87-773, 1987-1988 (Reel 39, Frame 571)
    - Board of Global Ministries, North Arkansas Conference, United Methodist Church, Arkansas Women's Training Project, 81-255, 1982 (Reel 39, Frame 590)
    - Board of Global Ministries, North Arkansas Conference, United Methodist Church, Arkansas Women's Training Project, 81-1005, 1980-1982 (Reel 39, Frame 607)
    - Board of Global Ministries, North Arkansas Conference, United Methodist Church, Arkansas Women's Project, 82-314, 1983-1984 (Reel 39, Frame 625)
    - Board of Global Ministries, North Arkansas Conference, United Methodist Church, Arkansas Women's Project, 85-478, 1985-1986 (Reel 39, Frame 641)
    - Boston Mountain Educational Cooperative, 93-112, 1993-1994 (Reel 39, Frame 672)
    - Boy Scouts of America, South Central Region, 81-206, 1981 (Reel 39, Frame 714)
    - Boy Scouts of America, 94-94, 1994-1998 (Reel 39, Frame 737)
    - Boys, Girls, Adults Community Development Center, Incorporated, B.G.A.C.D.C, 84-406, 1984-1985 (Reel 39, Frame 948)
    - Boys, Girls, Adults Community Development Center, Incorporated, B.G.A.C.D.C, 85-479, 1985-1986 (Reel 39, Frame 979)
    - Boys, Girls, Adults Community Development Center, Incorporated, B.G.A.C.D.C, 86-588, 1986-1987 (Reel 39, Frame 1009)
    - Boys, Girls, Adults Community Development Center, Incorporated, B.G.A.C.D.C, 87-757, 1987-1988 (Reel 40, Frame 1)
    - Boys, Girls, Adults Community Development Center, Incorporated, B.G.A.C.D.C, Community Education Support, 88-53, 1988-1991 (Reel 40, Frame 23)
    - Boys, Girls, Adults Community Development Center, Incorporated, B.G.A.C.D.C, 90-94, 1990-1991 (Reel 40, Frame 111)
    - Boys, Girls, Adults Community Development Center, Incorporated, B.G.A.C.D.C, 91-114, 1990-1992 (Reel 40, Frame 151)
    - Boys, Girls, Adults Community Development Center, Incorporated, B.G.A.C.D.C, 91-156, 1991-1993 (Reel 40, Frame 250)
    - Boys, Girls, Adults Community Development Center, Incorporated, B.G.A.C.D.C, 94-162, Original Proposal-Year One, 1994-1997 (Reel 40, Frame 317)
    - Boys, Girls, Adults Community Development Center, Incorporated, B.G.A.C.D.C, 94-162, Year Two-Year Three, 1995-1998 (Reel 40, Frame 590)
    - Boys, Girls, Adults Community Development Center, Incorporated, B.G.A.C.D.C, Professional Services Agreement, 1994 (Reel 40, Frame 888)
    - Bradford Special School District, 88-109, 1988-1989 (Reel 40, Frame 909)
    - Bragg, Ronald E., Professional Services Agreement, 1995-1996 (Reel 40, Frame 928)
    - Break the Mold, Process Observer, Professional Services Agreement, 1995 (Reel 40, Frame 944)
    - Break the Mold, Process Observer, Bishop, Mona, Professional Services Agreement, 1994-1996 (Reel 40, Frame 949)
    - Break the Mold, Process Observer, Cook, Thelma, Professional Services Agreement, 1994-1996 (Reel 40, Frame 962)
    - Break the Mold, Process Observer, Coston, Shari, Professional Services Agreement, 1996 (Reel 40, Frame 974)
    - Break the Mold, Process Observer, Dalton, Susan, Professional Services Agreement, 1994-1996 (Reel 40, Frame 981)
    - Break the Mold, Process Observer, Futterer, Margaret, Professional Services Agreement, 1994-1996 (Reel 40, Frame 996)
    - Break the Mold, Process Observer, Garrett, David, Professional Services Agreement, 1994-1995 (Reel 40, Frame 1023)
    - Break the Mold, Process Observer, Gathright, Diann, Professional Services Agreement, 1995-1996 (Reel 40, Frame 1031)
    - Break the Mold, Process Observer, McCarty, Beth, Professional Services Agreement, 1994-1996 (Reel 40, Frame 1054)
    - Break the Mold, Process Observer, Nesson, Ralph, Professional Services Agreement, 1994-1997 (Reel 40, Frame 1083)
    - Break the Mold, Process Observer, Russell, Charles, Professional Services Agreement, 1994-1996 (Reel 40, Frame 1114)
    - Break the Mold, Process Observer, Thomas, Diane, Professional Services Agreement, 1994-1996 (Reel 40, Frame 1129)
    - Break the Mold, Process Observer, Tyler, Tommy, Professional Services Agreement, 1994-1996 (Reel 41, Frame 1)
    - Brookland Public Schools, Brookland High School, 89-19, 1989 (Reel 41, Frame 12)
    - Brown, Robert L., Professional Services Agreement, 1987 (Reel 41, Frame 27)
    - Bryant Public Schools, 86-568, 1986 (Reel 41, Frame 47)
    - Bryant Public Schools, 87-744, 1987-1988 (Reel 41, Frame 64)
    - Bryant Public Schools, 90-47, 1990 (Reel 41, Frame 81)
    - Bryant Public Schools, 91-90, 1991-1992 (Reel 41, Frame 125)
    - Bryant Public Schools, 93-165, 1993-1994 (Reel 41, Frame 159)
    - Bryant Public Schools, 94-142, 1994-1995 (Reel 41, Frame 189)
    - Buffalo Island Central School District, 94-5, 1994 (Reel 41, Frame 238)
    - C Results, Professional Services Agreement, 1993 (Reel 41, Frame 278)
    - Cabot High School, 85-552, 1985-1986 (Reel 41, Frame 293)
    - Cabot Public Schools, 87-761, 1987-1988 (Reel 41, Frame 315)
    - Cabot Public Schools, 87-836, 1987-1988 (Reel 41, Frame 336)
    - Cabot Public Schools. West side Elementary School, 89-115, 1990-1991 (Reel 41, Frame 358)
    - Cabot Public Schools, 90-15, 1989-1990 (Reel 41, Frame 378)
    - Cabot Public Schools, 92-16, 1991-1992 (Reel 41, Frame 454)
    - Cabot Public Schools, 93-141, 1993-1994 (Reel 41, Frame 493)
    - Cabot Public Schools, 94-178, 1994-1995 (Reel 41, Frame 531)
    - Cabot Public Schools, 95-133, 1995-1996 (Reel 41, Frame 575)
    - Cabot Public Schools, 95-150, 1995-1996 (Reel 41, Frame 613)
    - Caddo Hills School District, 93-23, 1993 (Reel 41, Frame 692)
    - Calico Rock School District, Calico Rock Elementary School, 90-43, 1989-1991 (Reel 41, Frame 734)
    - Camden Public Schools, 90-81, 1990-1991 (Reel 41, Frame 785)
    - Camden Fairview School District, 94-88, 1994-1998 (Reel 41, Frame 828)
    - Camp Aldersgate, Incorporated, Youth-at-Risk Program, 80-1001, 1980 (Reel 41, Frame 961)
    - Camp Aldersgate, Incorporated, Youth-at-Risk Program, 81-246, 1981 (Reel 41, Frame 974)
    - Camp Mitchell, Camp and Conference Center, 82-265, 1982-1983 (Reel 41, Frame 986)
    - Campbell and Associates, Professional Services Agreement, 1993 (Reel 41, Frame 1003)
    - Carson Communications, Professional Services Agreement, 1990-1992 (Reel 41, Frame 1014)
    - Kit Carson Photography, Professional Services Agreement, 1993 (Reel 41, Frame 1022)
    - Carthage Public Schools, Principal School Improvements, 93-213, 1993-1997 (Reel 41, Frame 1027)
    - Case, Charles, Professional Services Agreement, 1991 (Reel 41, Frame 1154)
    - Cats Climb, Incorporated, 87-835, 1988 (Reel 41, Frame 1160)
    - Cavanaugh, Hagan and Pierson, Incorporated, Professional Services Agreement, 1991-1993 (Reel 42, Frame 1)
    - Cavanaugh, Hagan and Pierson, Incorporated, Professional Services Agreement, 1994 (Reel 42, Frame 84)
    - Cedarville Public Schools, 89-12, 1989 (Reel 42, Frame 96)
    - Cedarville Public Schools, 89-103, 1989-1991 (Reel 42, Frame 109)
    - Cedarville Public Schools, 91-99, 1991-1992 (Reel 42, Frame 126)
    - Cedarville Public Schools, 92-167, 1992-1993 (Reel 42, Frame 167)
    - Center for Education and Communication, 81-232, 1981-1983 (Reel 42, Frame 208)
    - Center to Prevent Handgun Violence, 90-38, 1988-1991 (Reel 42, Frame 227)
    - Centers for Youth and Families, Project Safe Place, 90-102, 1988-1993 (Reel 42, Frame 495)
    - Centers for Youth and Families, 94-92, Original Proposal-Year One, 1994-1997 (Reel 42, Frame 719)
    - Centers for Youth and Families, 94-92, Year Two-Year Four, 1995-1998 (Reel 42, Frame 984)
    - Central Arkansas Area Agency on Aging, Incorporated, Share-A-Home, 80-1002, 1980 (Reel 43, Frame 1)
    - Central Arkansas Area Agency on Aging, Incorporated, Share-A-Home, 81-233, 1981-1983 (Reel 43, Frame 13)
    - Central Arkansas Legal Services, Client Empowerment Project, 81-1001, 1981 (Reel 43, Frame 28)
    - Central Arkansas Legal Services, Client Empowerment Project, 82-266, 1981-1982 (Reel 43, Frame 43)
    - Central Arkansas Legal Services, Legal Self-Help (3rd Year), 83-320, 1983-1984 (Reel 43, Frame 60)
    - Central Arkansas Library System, 81-234, 1981 (Reel 43, Frame 83)
    - Central Arkansas Radiation Therapy Institute, 78-1007, 1977-1979 (Reel 43, Frame 94)
    - Central Arkansas YWCA, 80-1003, 1980 (Reel 43, Frame 106)
    - Central Baptist Hospital, HMO, 80-1004, 1980 (Reel 43, Frame 118)
    - City of Blevins, 88-101, 1988-1989 (Reel 43, Frame 133)
    - City of Dermott, 92-190, Original Proposal-Year One, 1992-1994 (Reel 43, Frame 153)